<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web-Development on Jordi Jaspers</title>
    <link>https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/tags/web-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web-Development on Jordi Jaspers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 15:22:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/tags/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio In Hugo &amp; Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/blog/personal-hugo-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 15:22:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/blog/personal-hugo-website/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: A personal webpage is a perfect place to let the world know about you and showcase your past accomplishments. Put your resume, your projects, your blogs in with a personalized theme which makes people know you have a great taste: all-in-one! It’s your portfolio displayed online, a small yet cool project you can do with not much effort, why not?
With Github Pages, we can host a personal webpage without bothering about finding a domain name, and with Hugo, we have a variety of themes to choose from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxy Servers</title>
      <link>https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/blog/proxies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 17:17:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordi-jaspers.github.io/blog/proxies/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Internet has connected people across the world using social media and audio/video calling features along with providing an overabundance of knowledge and tools. All this comes with an inherent danger of security and privacy breaches. In this guide we will talk about proxies which play a vital role in mitigating these risks.
Proxy Server Every web request which is sent from the client to a web server goes through some type of proxy server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
